Good morning.
早安
Hey!
喂!
Woops, sorry!
喔! 不好意思!
I didn't see you down there.
我沒看到你在下面
Oh. Heh!, eh... no problem.
喔...(乾笑)! 嗯....沒關係
I should really watch where I'm going.
我走路也應該注意
What are you doing down there anyway?
你還在下面幹嘛?
Everyone's heading South in a few hours.
幾個小時後 大家都要飛往南方了
Oh, I... I... eh, I dropped something.
喔, 我...我... 我有東西掉了
Yeah, you guys go on ahead, eh I'll follow you on.
你們先走 我隨後跟上
Eh... who's this guy?
那是誰啊?
I never got your name?
我還不知道你的名字呢?
It's Dougal.
我叫杜格
Hi Dougal, my name's Lucy.
嗨 杜格, 我叫露西。
This is Dick.
這位是迪克
Hi Dick.
嗨 迪克
Come on Lucy, let's get the flock outta here.
走吧 露西, 我們趕緊離開這兒吧
Nice to meet you Dougal,
很高興認識你 杜格,
I guess I'll see you down there!
那就到時候見囉!
Good Morning.
早安
Can I have ten packs of beetle husks,
我要10包甲蟲殼,
five tins of hazel nut butter,
5罐榛果奶油,
eight packs of dried elderberries,
8包接骨木乾
one pot of honey,
1壺蜂蜜,
a half case of nettle tea,
半盒蕁麻茶,
two doz... ten packs of fresh poppyseed,
兩打...10包新鮮的罌粟籽
two tins of rose-hip syrup
2罐玫瑰果糖漿
and a box of fennel mash.
還有1盒茴香末
Oh, and how much for that plant?
喔, 還有 那個盆栽多少錢?
Now, where to put you?
現在, 應該要把你擺在哪呢?
Perfect.
很好
We'll be fine.
我們會很好的
Plenty more rain on the way,
即將會有更多雨水,
with showers due to continue right through to the end of...
及連續陣雨直到...
I don't care about the accident I s...
我不管那個意外, 我...
And if you do continue to eat these worms
如果你持續食用那些綜合昆蟲
combined of course with regular...
當然是以一般...
We are down here in the Sunny South
我們現在位於陽光南方,
and just check out some of these chicks!
先來看看這些美眉吧!
Lucy?
露西?
There's nothing left.
沒有剩下任何東西
I've gotta get out of here.
我一定要離開這。
But how? I can't fly.
可是怎麼走?我不能飛。
Of Course you can fly- you're a bird.
你當然能飛, 你是隻鳥耶
If I stay I'll freeze to death.Or starve!
如果我留下來 我會被凍死或餓死!
I shouldn't even be here.
我根本不應該在這。
I should be down south with the others.
我應該跟大夥一起在南方
I could be on the beach with Lucy.
我可以跟露西一起在海灘。
You don't want to end up like him!
你不想最後變得跟它一樣!
I've gotta do it.
我必須要這麼做
This is it.
走吧
Ha! I did it, I'm flying, I'm really flying!
哈! 我做到了, 我在飛, 我真的在飛!
Welcome to the sunny south!
歡迎來到陽光南方!
Hey, Dougal, great to see you!
嗨, 杜格! 很高興看到你!
Lucy, this place, it's amazing!
露西, 這裡好棒喔!
Yeah, Dick and I were wondering
是啊, 迪克跟我還在想
if you were gonna make it.
你會不會來
Oh yeah, Dick.
喔對, 迪克
Hey Dick, look who it is.
迪克, 看看誰來了
Hey Dougal!
嗨 杜格!
Oh. Hey Dick. So you guys aren't...
喔, 嗨 迪克 所以你們不是....
Noooo!
不是!
Ahhhh.
啊....
Dougal, now that you're here,
杜格, 現在你在這,
I wanted to ask you something.
我想問你一件事情
Yeah Lucy?
什麼事 露西?
Do you... wanna go for a swim?
你想.......去游泳嗎?
Swim? Hu! Eh, OK!
游泳? 喔! 嗯..好啊!